Lesson three, Ted's day at school.
Ted tells his parents he did poorly on his chemistry test.
They tell him he needs to get serious and study more.
How was your day at school today, Ted?
Bad.
I had a chemistry test and I blew it.
Maybe if you didn't cut class so often, you'd do better.
That's right son.
Stop slacking off and start hitting the books.
But I can't stand chemistry class.
Besides, it's a lost cause.
That class is way over my head.
You need to buckle down.
When I'm a famous musician, people won't give a hoot about my knowledge of atoms and
molecules.
That's beside the point.
We know you have your heart set on going to New York University.
And you don't stand a chance of getting in there with such poor grades.